Even though we're both girls...
Yamada, you're with me!
We're in the same class!
That's great!
Oh! I'm also there!
Me and the pretty tall girl...
started dating a little while ago...
Huh? Kase?
W-What's going on?
Ye... ah... Sure...
H-Hello? This is Yamada speaking!
Uh...
I... I know.
It's Kase, silly.
Yeah, of course.
I knew it couldn't be anyone else,
b-but I got all tense for some reason.
What's up with that?
Anyways, whatcha up to?
Right now?
I got out of the shower
and thought I'd do a little reading.
You know me, I love going
through gardening books.
Oh, gardening.
Fun.
There's something I have to tell you...
Yeah? What is it?
This is my first time doing something like this.
I've never dated, talked to boys,
or anything like that.
Y-You're the first person I've gone out with.
G-Gosh, this is so embarrassing
to say at my age.
No! You don't have to be embarrassed about anything!
Couples are supposed to be doing all sorts of things, right?
I don't know much about it, so—
What was that noise? A-Are you there? Hello?
Huh, weird.
I-It's nothing...
Are you okay?
You sound kinda out of breath.
I know training and stuff is important,
but don't overdo it.
Kase?
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
Really? That's a relief.
As my girlfriend,
is there anything you'd like me to do?
U-Um...
You there, Kase?
Kase?!
You don't...
Just do whatever feels right.
Huh?
Is that all?
Yeah.
Guess I overthought it.
Well then, goodnight.
Will you... go out with me?
It's not like...
It's not like I don't want to...
It's okay if you don't feel the same... I'm sorry...
I've actually felt the same way for a long time...
I can't believe I'm really dating her!
I love Kase... and she loves me back!
Oh gosh, I don't know what to do!
Just do whatever feels right.
Dating's nothing like I thought.
It's so much more vague than I imagined.
Even so, there's one thing that always works.
I'm gonna make her a bento lunch!
Huh?! Is Kase absent today?!
No, she left 'cause her club needed her.
Some track thing, I think.
That's basically the same thing!
I should just go back to bed...
You gonna sleep on the floor?
This'll be my first time in Okinawa!
And my first time flying!
Okay, everyone, settle down.
If you guys get all worked up now,
you'll burn out before we even get there.
Not gonna happen! We're all young!
You got that right!
Who said anything about age?
Are you guys trying to imply something?
This trip is gonna be lit! Right, Yamada?
Heya!
Working hard as always, gardening prez!
Oh, it's just you.
What's with that reaction, Miss Sigher? I came to cheer you up, you know.
Miss Sigher?
Was I sighing or something?
Well, see ya 'morrow!
Bye-bye.
Yeah, see you.
Was I really sighing?
No! Don't get distracted!
Oh! I heard it just now!
Yamada! Good Mornin'!
Morning, Kase!
Listen, I, uh...
Well, I...
Morning, Kase!
That hurt! What the heck are you doing?
It was so boring without you yesterday.
Come with us to Class C!
Suzuki still hasn't written a single thing
for the article she said she'd do!
Seriously? Still nothing?
I tried talking to her, but nothing.
We need you to give her a good talking-to!
Yeah!
Please!
Save us, Kase!
Kase sure is popular, huh?
Yeah, she is.
Oh well.
I'll just tell her when lunch rolls around.
Yamada! Wanna eat lunch with me?
Oh, actually, I'm having lunch with Kase today.
Huh? Didn't she go to the cafeteria
with her track club?
What?!
Sleepin' on the floor again?
Yamada, are you...
Are you and Kase dating?
Wh-Why do you ask?!
Kinda seems that way.
I mean, you even packed 2 lunches...
I-I, uh, um...
You should've told me!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to, but you know...
Here.
I've never experienced it myself,
but going out with someone
that popular must be hard, right?
That said, I'm certain you're up to the task.
Huh? Is it empty?
I'm so sorry! I'll make it up to you next time!
Hey, why do you have so many leftovers?
Oh! Kase!
Yum!
That was great!
Thanks for making it!
Sorry about lunch. It never crossed my mind
that you'd make me something.
It's always so chaotic around me
I kinda get lost.
It's fine.
You're one of the kindest
and coolest girls I've met.
I'm not surprised everyone
wants to be around you.
Yamada?
Makes me think...
There must've been loads
of important things I've missed in the past.
Hmm?
Grab my hand!
Uh, okay.
This way!
Right here. Take a look.
Flowerbeds?
Back in our second year, you used to
come here after lunch and pull weeds,
even though you barely had
any time before the bell.
You'd work your way along the bushes,
from one end to the next.
When it rained, you had a green umbrella.
Other times, you had a straw hat.
I couldn't believe how amazing you were.
I was always praying you'd notice me up here.
But somehow, you never did.
Even if I was looking at you every day.
I sound like a creep, right?
Any way you look at it, I'm a total stalker!
I've been the gardening prez stalker
this whole time!
Kase...
But in the end, I got my wish.
You've noticed me.
Yeah!
Kase and I started going out this spring.
I'm pretty simple.
I love plants and I'm in the gardening club.
Kase, on the other hand, is an incredible runner
who got our track club to Nationals three times.
You'd think I'd be all nervous and stuff
because we're both girls,
but I've just never dated anyone before.
I love her so much...
that I don't know what to do with myself...
Yamada! Are you free today?
Hmm?
I don't have practice today.
Just a short meeting and then I'm free.
Oh wow! That's rare!
Wanna come over?
R-Really?!
Yeah! My parents are both working late tonight.
I'd be kinda lonely all alone.
I-I see...
Well, if you insist...
Yippie!
Okay then.
Alrighty, I'll go drop off my bag at home first.
Okkie. See ya in a bit.
Se— Ouch!
Kase?!
No worries. I'm fine.
What's gotten into her?
Oh well. I better get going. Lots of things to do at home.
Alright, let's go over everything.
No new messages, no change of plans.
Room cleaning: check! Desk: check!
Covers: check!
Everything's perfect!
All that's missing is Kase.
We have the whole place to our own.
Wait...
isn't being alone with her kind of a big deal?
Yes?
H-Hello!
Kase! Welcome! Was the house hard to find?
Heh, no sweat!
I installed all the map apps on my phone so—
You did? Guess you had no trouble then.
I, um, bought something on the way.
Cake?
Wanna give it a taste?
Yeah!
It's a little messy, but come on in.
T-Thanks for having me.
Kinda embarrassing,
but I tidied the whole room.
Here!
H-Huh?
Take a seat while I go make some tea.
O-Okay...
I can't believe Kase is actually in my room!
Gosh, this is so embarrassing!
But I couldn't be happier right now.
Sorry it—
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
N-No, everything's fine!
I was just admiring how comfy your bed is!
Oh, that's what it is.
You have a lot of books, don't you?
Oh, this one's all in English.
It's published by the UK's National Trust.
They're an environmental nonprofit.
Huh.
The UK is something of a mecca for gardeners.
I'd love to go there someday.
A-Are you planning to move to England?!
Huh? No way, I can't speak English at all!
I just meant it'd be nice to visit.
Oh...
You're really amazing, Yamada.
Really? I don't think so...
We should try the cake!
Strawberry Shortcakes!
Here, you can have mine.
I know you love strawberries.
Huh? Y-You're not wrong,
but aren't they the best part?
I won't take no for an answer.
Say "ahh."
Tasty as it looks?
Mm-hm!
I think I'll eat mine on the bed, too.
Shortcakes are one of your favorites, right?
Yep!
Yamada...
Hm?
Do you... um...
want to...
Do you want to do it... with me?
Hm?
That a "no"?
Does she mean a kiss?
Does she want to kiss me?
I, um...
O-Okay...
If you want to, I want to as well.
Oh, but let me finish this tea first.
H-Hot!
You're totally clueless, aren't you?
Sorry, I got carried away a little
'cause we're in your room.
Forget I said anything.
I-I knew what you meant!
Liar. You don't know squat.
I'm not lying! I really do know what you meant!
And if you wanna do it, I—
Are you sure, Yamada?
I wanna be your girlfriend in every way.
Every.
In every way?
You mean...
Kase smells so nice.
It kinda reminds me of herbs.
I wonder what it is...
Hello?
Yeah, I'm home.
Uh-huh. Okay.
I'm having a friend over. And she brought cake.
Huh? I didn't hear you.
Of course I thanked her!
Got it. Geez Mom, I know!
Yeah. I will.
Alright, see you soon.
Th-That was my mom.
She said she's coming home.
W-What?
That totally freaked me out!
Is your phone on max volume or something?
I-I'll check but I don't...
Looks like it might've been...
Yamada, come sit next to me.
Ouchy.
Down we go!
Let's save it for next time.
N-Next time?
Man, I'm so glad I didn't have practice today!
This was so much fun!
I don't think I'll be able to sleep tonight!
By the way, what's that smell on you?
It's very fragrant.
Oh, sorry! I didn't realize I was sweaty.
No no, nothing like that! I just noticed
a nice herby scent when we were lying down.
It was kinda... uh... lemongrassy.
Lemon?
Oh!
It's probably this.
I usually put it on after practice.
Wanna try? It's a body spray.
Oh!
Wow! Chilly!
Oh, that's it! That's the nice herby scent!
It's just like lemongrass!
Can we stay like this for a little while, Yamada?
That lemongrassy scent stayed on me...
long after that.
I lost count of how long it's been...
We're in the sky!
We're actually flying through the sky!
And they even gave us drinks!
Flying might be the best thing in the world!
Hey, Mikey!
I didn't want to take it off.
But now I'm feeling a little
under the weather so—
Mikey, are you okay?
I-I-I'll be in the toilet!
Is she gonna be alright?
Wow! This tastes so exotic!
What does?
This mix of orange and black tea! It's awesome!
What are you on about?
I'm serious!
I'm kinda feeling sick myself...
I'll put on some music to cancel out the noises.
Try some if you think I'm lying!
God, you're so annoying!
Here.
Fine.
Hey, Yamada, come with me for a sec.
K-Kase?
Where are we...
This is it! Look!
Isn't it grea—
This is amazing!
Did you know that the sun always shines
above the clouds?
Uh... I-I did. I think.
When I'm feeling sad about something,
when I'm mopey and sulking, or when one of my flowers dies,
I think about how the sun shines
above the gloomy clouds.
Doesn't knowing that make you feel
like you can push through anything?
Yeah, it sure does.
The other day, when another club
made a complaint against me,
I thought about something similar.
The girl running next to me fell,
and their team insisted I tripped her.
After they argued with the judges,
we had to redo the race.
I ended up winning regardless.
Everyone's just trying to shine their brightest.
Maybe a little too much sometimes.
But let me tell ya,
seeing the sky makes
all those things seem small.
The sun really has a lot of power, doesn't it?
Wow! The sky is a totally different color here!
Their Hibiscus's are already blooming!
Ground my beloved.
Hey, Mikey!
What are you taking pics for?!
I was just happy you were feeling better.
She's adorable.
That hit the spot.
Try this, Yamada.
That's so good!
Oh! Sorry! Here.
Wow, it's sour and sweet.
Nope.
When did you get here?
Come on now, cuties like you two
need a proper photo.
Alrighty, say cheese!
Yamada, wanna get matching souvenirs?
Yeah! Let's get something
we can carry around with us all the time.
How cliché of you.
Is that a bad thing?
Neither here nor there.
I'm so confused...
Oh, there's Kase!
Mind helping us choose souvenirs for juniors?
O-Oh. Sure! Be right there!
Sorry. I'll text ya later.
Okay.
Kase and I were staying in different hotel rooms.
Look! We have an ocean view!
Left side's mine, thank you very much.
Hey, no fair!
Comfy beds and an ocean view...
Total jackpot!
Geez...
I was happy I got to share a room with Mikey,
but I was kinda hoping to stay with Kase.
Score! No one's here!
Woah! It's so pretty inside.
Huh? Why?!
What did you guys end up buying?
Uh, one of those "chinsu" thingies.
I-I forgot I'd be naked in front of Kase...
Bit too late to worry about that.
I'll be inside if you need me!
This bath is huge!
How about a race?
Not swimming, dummy.
Yamada, am I making things weird for you?
This is nothing unusual for me.
Me and the other clubs girls
see each other naked all the time.
But if I make you feel uncomfortable,
I'll try to n-not look your way.
Kase, are you coming or what?
I wanna show you how fast I am!
Again, no swimming.
You're guys are so annoying!
I'm coming in a sec!
I'm going in.
I-I think I'll use the bath in my room...
Um...
I'll answer her tomorrow.
Yeah.
Why? Why am I like this?
What gives, Yamada?
The rest of the day is free time for your groups.
Be careful not to get separated!
That's all. Dismissed.
Come with me.
You don't have to cry, Yamada.
I'm the one being dumped, after all.
I was afraid this would happen.
That you'd see me naked
and stop wanting to be with me.
Similar things happened before.
Friends would suddenly stop talking to me
after seeing me change in the locker room.
I guess... we're at that point—
You're wrong!
It's nothing like that! I was just surprised!
Huh?
That was the first time I've seen you
without clothes and I panicked.
My body is all soft and squishy compared to yours...
I couldn't bring myself to take my clothes in front of you...
I didn't mean anything else by it!
I'm so sorry, Kase!
Kase?
That's all it was...
I feel like a boulder's off my chest!
Let's come back here.
Huh?
To Okinawa, I mean.
But just the two of us next time.
Sure!
It's a promise.
I'll never forget that coral.
Or how it smelled like summer.
Hello?
Oh, hey!
It's been a while.
I'm actually just about to go in there.
Yeah.
I'll be honest, the nevers are killing me, prez.
She'll have no problems getting into Seigyoku.
Really?
I'd recommend some English lessons,
just to be safe.
Thank you for the good news.
You better work hard, Yui.
Yeah.
Yamada!
Kase!
Were you at your counseling? How'd it go?
Uh...
fine...
I've decided to take the entrance exam
for Nikkyo University.
Oh...
I see...
Even with a recommendation,
no guarantees I'll actually get in.
If anyone can get in, it's you!
You think so?
I do!
How did yours go?
Good...
Where did you apply to?
I went with a local one in the end.
Seigyoku Womens University.
My parents like it because it's close to home.
I-I see..
You made a good choice!
I heard it's a great school!
I think it'll suit you.
Yeah.
And that area has a ton of greenery.
So? Will the gardening prez
admit defeat to this heavy rain?
Be it rain, be it extreme heat,
this gardener never takes a day off!
Alright! I'll help out!
But you don't have a cover.
It'll be fine!
That one's up next.
The Hortensia?
Yeah!
Wh-Where should I put it?
Right there. Next to the red pot.
Okay, ready, set...
Upsy-daisy.
Those flowers sure have it good.
Wish I could be in your care like that.
Huh?
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
I wanna be your flower.
You'd fight off weeds and bugs for me,
give me water when I'm thirsty...
Bet I'd grow into a pretty amazing one!
What are you saying?
Dontcha think it'd be really fun?
Wait! You're gonna get wet!
Kase as a flower?
In a lot of ways,
she was already kind of like my flower.
If you asked me which one, a sunflower.
A beautiful tall flower that never stops
trying to reach the shining sun.
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Why'd you choose a literature course?
Huh?
W-Well...
Excuse me for a sec.
Yes, hello?
You heard right. I'm gonna try for it, after all.
Oh? Okay.
Really?
I see.
I'm with a friend right now.
Mind if we continue this later?
See ya tomorrow.
Y-Yeah.
See ya.
Why'd you choose a literature course?
Really, Yamada?
You're going with Seigyoku?
So you're staying here, huh.
Anyways, what about you?
I'm probably gonna go with... whichever I get in.
Wow! You're so chill about this!
That's how I choose to live my life!
Yamada, are you sure about this?
About what?
About Kase! Didn't she get a recommendation
for a sports university in Tokyo?
It's not like it's a done deal.
It basically is!
It's not!
Seniors usually quit their clubs before summer,
but Kase is still in hers and running every day.
You gotta face reality, Yamada.
Can't hear you. Don't wanna hear you.
What are you planning on doing
if she goes to Tokyo?
I don't know. Nothing's sure yet.
Geez louise. But maybe it's for the best.
Huh?
You and I only became friends
after starting high school.
Before then, we didn't even know
the other existed.
You're right.
Students like us constantly go through the same "new school-new friend" cycle.
Yeah.
Once Kase moves to a new school,
she'll have all kinds of fun new encounters.
Take a look.
Come on, stop that, Kase.
You're totally enjoying it.
Yo— wr—
K-Kase?
Right?
C'mon.
Kase?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Kase! Don't go!
I'm off!
Yui, wait! You forgot your bag.
I did?
Pull yourself together, honey.
Mornin' Kase!
Another tough practice this morning?
Morning.
Morning, Yamada.
M-Morning.
What...
am I doing?
Once we graduate, it could be over between us.
It'll be too late soon.
Before then, I want to talk...
for hours on end.
Before then, I want to hang out...
every single day...
Hello?
What's wrong, Yamada?
Huh?
Did I... do something wrong?
Nothing at all.
Are you mad because I'm going to Tokyo?
I'm not mad! I'm really not!
Right, I'm being silly.
We don't even know if I'll even get in.
Y-You will! I know it!
Yamada, I...
Huh?
I... don't want to be away from you.
The other day... I got so overwhelmed...
I asked Coach to switch my recommendation
to a local sports university.
To switch?
It turned into such a big deal
I got called into principals.
I had no idea...
I really... want to be here with you, Yamada.
I... can call you every day
no matter where you are!
And I'll visit you during breaks!
So please...
give that test everything you've got.
Thank you, Yamada.
Of course.
That was the day Kase left for Tokyo.
Kase!
Tomorrows's the big day!
You betcha.
I'm taking a bullet train later.
Best of luck out there!
Thank you.
Did this area got bigger of something?
Oh, you noticed?
Of course. I know this place very well.
I think you're the only person
other than me that can say that.
The festival is soon, and the band
and orchestra will be using this space
I trimmed everything to give them more space.
Seems kind of a waste.
It's only fair. This space belongs to everyone.
You always go on about how great I am,
but I think you're the one who's really great.
Huh?
You're amazing.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh, okay.
I'm heading out now.
After we graduate...
all kinds of new encounters will await us.
See ya tonight.
One of my friends who lives in Tokyo
is gonna meet me at the station.
Talk about a great friend.
Oh, I see. That'll take some load off.
I'll never forget that sunset...
Good luck with the festival.
You too!
It was one of the prettiest sunsets I've ever seen.
Now that Kase's gone, school seems kinda quiet.
It feels empty.
That's not it!
The thing that feels empty...
is me!
I don't wanna be away from Kase!
I can't let us part here!
This is it Kase.
Give 'em hell.
I will, Coach!
Remember, your stop is the last one.
Coach, I'm not a little kid...
I'm going with you!
Yamada?!
I'm going to Tokyo!
I refuse to let you go!
Yamada!
Take me with you!
I wanna be close to you!
I can't stand being without you!
Yamada...
I can't!
Thank you for coming.
Do you know what
the morning glory flower symbolizes?
Morning glories?
They symbolize love.
That's right.
Do you know the other one?
"Everlasting bond."