Tomoka Kase
Kobayashi Yuka
Egami Yuri
TODAY
READ
Can I call you?
Class Trip Planning
Itinerary
Packing List
Assigning Duties
Bus stop
Nishiko High School
Main Entrance
Bicycle Parking
Gas and water bills
are due soon.
We're out of milk and mayo.
Mom
Mobile
EDIT
Ryukyu Shisa
SOUVENIRS
RYUKYU SOUVENIRS
Souvenirs
I'm gonna go check out the baths!
WOMEN
Kase
I'll see ya there
Wanna slip away over free time tomorrow?
read
same old sign
SPECIAL SCREENING
"MELODY"
WORK PRODUCED IN 1971
Same old just faded
Name: "Zephyranthes"
Me and Yamada found it near the shore where we sang.
Belongs to the Amaryllis family.
Blooms with white, yellow, and pink flowers.
Also known as "Rain Lily" because it blooms after rain.
RUNNER - AUTUMN SPECIAL EDITION
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO EXCEL ON THE TRACK
INCLUDES TRAINING PLANS FROM PROFESSIONALS IN THE FIELD