You were drenched in sweat when our eyes met,
shining brighter than anyone else in the world
I didn't understand what the feeling was,
but I was ready for a new journey with you
I'll never forget the breeze
as I watched you after the rain fell
One day, I'll shine bright enough to keep you warm
I want to write the longest love story with you,
coloring each page with our emotions, day after day
Like two stars lining up on a horoscope's page,
I couldn't stop wishing
our futures would intertwine
My heart, covered in old scars,
is finally starting to heal
Your love for it
will make it beat like never before
Somewhere along the way,
the emptiness in my heart started to disappear,
quietly being filled
with fleeting moments I had with you
I want to look into your beautiful eyes forever
and smile as you share
your most intimate dreams
When I think about how much
I want to be your knight in shining armor,
it gives me all the courage
to take a step forward
Before I met you,
I was always afraid of getting hurt,
always choosing to take the long way around
My tough exterior has nowhere to go anymore,
surrounded by the emotions I feel
when I'm around you
That day, when I learend of your true feelings,
my overflowing tears
said more than any words could
Even if our paths won't always
have the same road ahead
I'm determined to walk with you side by side
Let's take a blank canvas
and paint it in our dreams,
I've been searching for an excuse
to show you how I feel
I don't want the melody
of our love to stop playing
As I hold back my tears,
fearing what your answer will be,
I ask you this question, made of simple words,
This bond will last forever, won't it?
My feelings for you are like raindrops
in the midnight clouds,
with nothing to stop them
from pouring down on you
Before my thoughts could catch up,
the wind after the rain had already come
and opened the doors of tomorrow
and our future
I want us to make a promise that outlives time,
crossing every season yet to come
and piercing eternity
When we finally reach our destination
after this long journey
we'll look back and smile at the love
we nurtured along the way